A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor Harry F. Byrd, 1926-1930
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Pardons, Requisitions, and Prison Affairs, 1922-1926., Extent: cu. ft. ( boxes) (Box Boxes 106-)
  - Subseries A. Pardons
    - Sailor - Satko (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Saunders - Sawyer (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Scanlon - Scott (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Seaburn - Sesler (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Shaffer - Sherman (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Shields - Shiflett (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Shirley - Showalter (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Shrader - Simpson (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Sims - Sizemore (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Skalak - Smith, Alfred (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Emmett - Smith, Fred (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - Smith, George - Smith, John (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Nellie - Smyth, Frank (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Snead - Sommers (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Speed - Sprouse (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Stanley - Staves (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Steber - Stewart (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Stidham - Stover (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Strange - Stump (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Sullivan - Switzer (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Tabb - Taylor (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Teaster - Tester (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Thomas (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - Thompson - Toombs (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - Trayer - Turlington (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Turner - Tyler (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Updike, Giles (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Upton, George W. (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Valdeze - Vowell (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Wade - Wallace (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Walls - Waters (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Watkins - Wayne (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Weaver - Wells (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Werner - White (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Whitehead - Wilkins (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Williams, A.H. - Williams, Kearney (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Williams, Lorenzo - Williams, Willie (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Williamson - Wilson (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Wingfield - Woolf (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Wooton - Wyatt (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Yancey - Young (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Federal (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Fines (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Removal of disability of right to drive automobiles (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Other states (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 124, Folder 5-8)
    - Index cards (Box 137-138)
  - Subseries B. Requisitions
    - Able - Anglin (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Archer - Avey (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Babcock - Ballard (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Ballard, C.R. (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Banagan - Baynes (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Barnett, Willard (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Beane - Bivins (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Black - Boykins (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Bradford - Brooks (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Brown - Bryant- Byrum (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Buckholtz - Byrum (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Brown, A.R. (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Burton, Charles H. (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - B, Miscellaneous (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Cabe - Caudill (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Chadwell - Childs (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Clack - Cline (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Coffman - Comer (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - Conner - Cox (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Craig - Cutler (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Criminal charges (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Daisey - Day (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Dean - Derrick (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Dickens - Dixon (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Dobyns - Duty (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - East - Everhart (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - Faison - Floyd (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Fobbs - Fortune (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Forney, Charles (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Foster - Fulp (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Gamble - George (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Gibbs - Gorman (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Graham - Guthrow (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Hagy - Hankins (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Hardy - Haynes (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Heckney - Hite (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Hobbs - Hoyle (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Hubble - Hyman (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Ingle - Isabell (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Jackson - Jewett (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Johnson (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Jones - Joyner (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Keeton - Keyser (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Kilpatrick - Kyle (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Lacey - Lay (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Leach - Lewis (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Lindsay - Lynch (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - McBride - McQueen (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - McIlwaine, Gretchen (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Maclean - Marwitz (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Mason - Mays (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Meadows - Messina (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Michael - Mitchell (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Moll - Morrison (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Morse - Myers (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Nance - Nuckols (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Obst - Owen (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Pannill - Payne (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Peacock - Pettway (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Phelps - Pleasants (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Poindexter - Powers (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Pratt - Purks (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Quarters - Quinn (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Ramey - Reynolds (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Rhinehart - Ring (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Roberson - Ryan (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Roberts, H.E. (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Salmon - Sayers (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Scales - Seymour (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Sharitz - Shipp (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Shook - Shumaker (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Sibert - Sleigh (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Small - Smythe (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Snead - Sprouse (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Stafford - Stewart (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Stinchcomb - Sweet (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Talbott - Tester (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Thaxton - Tinsman (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Toddhurst - Tyree (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Tumlins, A.E. (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - U (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Valdeze - Viacellio (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Waddle - Waugh (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - Weatherly - Weston (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - Wheeler - Whitted (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - Widdop - Williamson (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - Willis - Witt (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Wolfe - Wynn (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Yacobosky - Younger (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Z (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Index cards [Renditions, Requisitions, Rewards, Designation of Judges, State Government Appointments) (Box 139-140)
    - Oversize, Misc. prisoners - Requisitions A-B (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - Oversize, Requisitions B-C (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - Oversize, Requisitions C-F (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Oversize, Requisitions G-J (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Oversize, Requisitions L-R (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - Oversize, Requisitions R-S (Box 143, Folder 14a)
    - Oversize, Requisitions W (Box 143, Folder 14b)
  - Subseries C. Prison Affairs
    - Letters from Prisoners, 1926 February-April (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Letters from Prisoners, 1926 May-July (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Letters from Prisoners, 1926 August-October (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Letters from Prisoners, 1926 November-December (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Letters from Prisoners, 1927 January-July (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Letters from Prisoners, 1927 August-December (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Letters from Prisoners, 1928 (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Letters from Prisoners, 1929-1930 (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - State Board of Public Welfare (Box 136, Folder 9)